

I am called Christy. I got hooked on Customer Support when I worked for Travelocity back in 1999. Since then I've used my empathy, talent for technical things, and enthusiasm for helping people to create positive customer experiences — by treating people with respect, digging deep into problems to find solutions, and not giving up until they're solved. I believe everyone is just trying to do their best, and sometimes they just need a friendly, confident person to help them do that.

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Type 81 words per minute
- Experienced in Microsoft office, Canva, Trello, Hootsuite, Basecamp, Gimp & more
- Explaining concepts clearly to teammates and customers via chat, email, and phone
- Subnetting
- HTML and CSS
- Currently learning Javascript



EDUCATION

BS in Business / Information
Technology, 2019 - Present
UNIVERSITY OF PHOENIX ONLINE
National Honors Society, Studying
Business and IT

VOLUNTEER WORK

Angel Food Ministries

INTERESTING LINKS



M. CHRISTINE VOLOSIN

CUSTOMER SUPPORT | JUNIOR DEVELOPER

CONTACT:

in <u>Christy Volosin LinkedIn</u>

christy.volosin2@gmail.com

(573) 263-4976

<u>Portfolio</u>

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Human Resources Professional Express Employment Professionals/ Sept 2019 - Mar 2020

- Singlehandedly managed all HR functions after company downsize, mastering the systems with minimal training, I was able to interview and train new coworkers resulting in a raise within my first week on the job.
- Manage Temp Associates through recruiting and screening, ensuring they were a great fit
 for the job and client, minimizing turnover and maintaining trusting relationship with
 clients.
- Placed job advertisements on 5 websites. Created tracking system, utilizing Google Sheets, for all internal coworkers to use as a solution to keep up with multiple application websites ensuring all relevant information was shared real time and decreasing overlapping applicant contact.
- Took job orders from Clients via phone, email, and in-person that were looking for
 Associates to fill open jobs, entered job orders into Express system. Reported to Owners of
 Express on a daily basis.
- Assisted with technical issues, both major and minor. Helped coworkers and applicants troubleshoot why a nationwide software update caused certain job application steps to no longer work, and showed them how to make them work. Installed battery backup for our server with assistance from national tech support.

Owner/Freelancer OraFlame Social Media, LLC/ June 2018 - Present

- Managed social media accounts for clients, managed a production calendar for an IT Director, and did voiceover work, among other small jobs.
- Had weekly and monthly meetings with clients to ensure deliverables were on time and meeting expectations. Communicated with clients via email, text, gmail chat, and phone.
- Created and updated IT production calendar on a biweekly basis, using Google Docs, publishing it to be seen by all members of the web development team. Maintained active communication with developers on team to reflect accurate projected project completion dates.
- Entered new projects and project details in Basecamp per directions from IT Director.
- Billed clients using either Wave online invoicing or via Upwork. Sent invoices with payment links via email.

Level I Tech Support Call Center Representative Hewlett-Packard Enterprises via Adecco Staffing/ June 2015 - Mar 2016

- Provided Level 1 technical support for employees in various departments of a large power grid company via phone and email.
- Performed password resets for over 20 platforms e.g. Active Directory, did remote
 desktop support via screen share, created support tickets, and escalated as needed.
 Documented each ticket with work done and pertinent information needed for next
 team.
- Took ownership of each call confidently and worked with each customer until any problems were solved. Showed empathy, built rapport and frequently was requested personally by customers and desktop support technicians alike.
- Received the highest Customer Satisfaction Scores manager had ever seen, positively impacting company's overall customer satisfaction percentages.